My son, my precious boy has been murdered!
I can sense the misfortune
that has befallen my son.
The bond between mother
and son has spoken!
My precious, beautiful boy, you
died covered with wounds like this!
Those bastards!
I can feel it!
I suffer the same pain you felt!
You were utterly magnificent as you
fought for Lord Dio, my dear centerfold!
How?
How did they do it to kill such
a noble and pure soul like you?
They must have done something underhanded!
Stop them!
The bastards!
I will make sure they pay a terrifying
price with the Empress card!
They'll regret the day they were born!
Move!
I won't stand idle!
This is the time for action!
A time for vengeance with a
stand that brings a slow death!
The anguish, the pain!
I shall kill them all!
Thank you.
Thank
you
so
much for watching.
You're the one who's going to die.
The one who's going to die.
We're the one who's going to die.
JoJo!
JoJo and crew, head to
the sacred city Varanasi.
Listen up.
I don't usually get on a soapbox like
this, but stupid people are just that.
You could repeat something a million
times over and they still won't listen.
You know the type, don't you?
There's just no helping the poor souls.
But you know, uh, hold on.
I never got your name, did I?
Nena.
Nena, that's a great name.
Daughter of a wealthy family in the sacred
city Varanasi that we're passing through,
right?
You're good looking, and you've got an
equally good head on your shoulders.
I have an eye for people,
which leads me to my point.
Hole Horse is a horrible
lying bastard, understand?
He was manipulating you.
Think how your parents would feel.
You hear me?
You can't end up like this, okay?
I know it's easy when you're in love,
but you can't afford to see the
world with such a narrow view.
Take a step back and look
at the whole picture.
Hey, we're almost there.
The city of Varanasi.
The sacred river, the Ganges.
A place for holy men,
the old and the sick, where domestic
animals and food for human consumption?
lie alongside human waste
and corpses for cremation.
The river embraces all.
From birth unto death, its holy
waters form a microcosm of life.
It is said that visitors of the sacred
city of Varanasi remain transfixed,
never wanting to leave.
Perhaps the landscape that is this
sacred land is a mirror unto the soul.
Hmm?
Man, this thing isn't getting any better.
What's wrong, old man?
You don't look well.
Uh-uh.
Looks like my bug bite
just got a lot worse.
This thing must be infected.
It's definitely swollen.
It would be best to have a doctor
look at it before it gets worse.
Hey, doesn't that sort of
look like a person's face?
Stop kidding around, Polnareff.
That's creepy.
Sorry about that.
Want me to go to the hospital with you?
No!
Stop treating me like an old man.
Hmm.
I'll just lance this. Huh?
What did you say?
It's definitely infected now.
It'll get worse if we
don't drain the fluid.
Hey, hey, hey, can't we just put medicine
and a bandage on it and call it a day?
Don't worry, my friend.
We'll numb the area so it won't hurt.
No problem.
No problem at all.
Come now, lie down.
Sir, I studied medicine in England.
I can do appendectomies, too.
Uh-oh, it's a little rusty.
Well, that's no problem.
All right, let's slice it open.
Come on, I don't want to
watch it being cut open.
Have a heart!
It'll be fine.
Hey, are you done yet?
Can I open my eyes now?
What the?
Hey, doctor!
Trying to cut me off?
That's a pretty stupid move, you old fart!
Choo-me-me!
What the...
what the hell is this?
I am the empress!
As in the empress part, old man Joseph!
And now, I'm gonna bloody you up blood!
When did you get on me, dammit?
No way, this thing's got teeth?
Damn thing's strong!
No, it grabbed the scalpel!
Oh, no!
Thank goodness that
was my artificial hand!
Bastard, think you can just cut me?
I'm a part of your body
now, old man Joseph!
You can't get away from me,
honey, no matter how hard you try.
You know, I bet I can tell you what's
going through that thick skull of yours.
You're probably thinking something like,
only a stand can beat another stand.
My stand, Hermit Purple, has the power
of clairvoyance and remote viewing.
But how am I supposed to fight
something like this with those powers?
How can I destroy something
that's growing out of my own arms?
So, honey, was that spot on?
Where's the user?
How in the hell could
you have infected me?
You moron! I won't tell!
Disgusting freak!
Running off to your friends?
We'll see how that goes, won't we?
Doctor, your next patient
is waiting for you.
Doctor!
Hey, don't get the wrong idea.
I didn't...
I killed him! Hey!
I'm Joseph Joestar, an American!
I'm staying at Hotel Clark's! What?!
And by the way, girly, I have a thing
for hot, young nurses like yourself.
I think I should give you an exam!
What?!
Wait! It's not true!
Oh, no!
Ha ha ha!
Now you can't go back to the hotel!
You're all alone now, honey!
I can kill you without anyone interfering!
You little...
you're pissing me off!
I'll crush you to tiny bits!
What? Hey!
This is your own arm!
Take care of it, you shitty old man!
It grew arms.
How much more could it grow?
What the hell?
Let go of it!
I mean it, freak! Now!
Not a chance!
Hey, officer!
The murderer's over here!
He's right here!
It's been a while since it's come to this.
Hey, what are you doing?
Overdrive!
Huh?
Moron!
It's your arm, remember?
You think your hamon would work against
your own body? Hands up! Don't move!
Then how about perfect purple?
You're crushing me!
I can use it this way too!
So how does it feel, ugly?
I told you not to move, now free!
Damn it! What are you
doing? I can't see! Shit!
Jesus, Mary and Joseph!
Do you get what I'm telling you, Nena?
Uh, real men don't have to talk a big
game like your six-shooting boyfriend.
That's how you figure out who's a
liar and who's the genuine article.
Damn cops have run me
in the wrong direction.
I'm nowhere near the hotel now.
If I had known this would happen, I
would have taken Polnareff with me.
Instead of a petty guy like
Whole Horse, why not be with me?
Am I not your type?
Come on, I don't dwell
on the past like some.
I don't care who you were
dating before even Whole Horse.
What's important is the future.
We just need to understand
each other, right?
Oh, look over there, Polnareff.
That place is a hotel run by a
nice Japanese woman named Kumiko.
She manages it with her Indian husband.
We can probably get a cheap room.
Oh, really?
Tell me more about this hotel.
What?
What the hell are you doing?!
Huh?
Jummy Man!
I'm eating, Joestar!
A growing girl needs her food!
You stole those at the market,
you quick little bastard!
Why, you...
Choo-me-mean!
Look how big I've gotten! It's tough!
Having another mouse to
feed isn't it, Daddy?
Choo-me-mean!
You disgusting little cow!
I'll show you that nobody
has the experience or
the smarts to take down
the great Joseph Joestar.
You don't stand a chance, you bastard!
Now how the hell am I
gonna do that? Damn it!
Here goes nothing.
Hermit Purple!
Oh, Daddy dearest, you've done
a wonderful job of raising me.
But you know, you shouldn't tie your
children down or they won't grow.
Oh, it only smothers them.
You should raise them to be free.
If not, they might rebel!
Oh, no!
It's no use.
If I had a camera,
I could use Hermit Purple to get a
picture of the Stan user's location.
Damn it all!
Come on, think, Joseph, think.
At this rate, it won't just be my arm.
She'll take over my whole body.
Huh?
Whoa!
I've already grown enough that I could
easily end your pathetic life. See?
My hand can reach your
throat now, old man.
I just have to bust
your carotid artery and
you'll crumple over
like a sack of potatoes.
Whoa!
Oh, no!
What's he doing?
Bastard!
He's lost his mind! Look at that!
Some very strange man has a
strange growth on his arm!
Damn it!
Where the hell's the stand user?
I have to tell you something. Huh?
I need a reliable man, a good
man like you, to take care of me.
And I love you, Polnareff.
Such a kind-hearted,
trustworthy man you are.
Really?
But it's all so sudden.
This is happening!
I have finally found one!
G-g-lucky!
Hey, Joseph Joestar, you idiot!
You keep getting farther and
farther from Jotaro and the others!
Do you really think I'm just
running around town randomly?
I'm not doing this just to
wear myself out, you know!
I'm running so I can kill you!
This is the end of the line!
See that?
You're going in!
Have a nice soap!
You senile old fool!
Yeah!
A nail?
Yeah, I picked it up earlier,
when you were rolling around
on the ground like an idiot.
Now I can shove it right in your carotid
and you'll bleed out like a stuck pig.
Did you actually believe I'd suffocate
if you stuck me in here, you fool!
Die!
I may be made of your flesh,
but I'm nothing like you!
Forget the rules already, Chunk!
Only a stand can hope to
defeat another stand! Oh, yeah!
Didn't you say you were gonna show me
all that fighting experience you have?
Was I supposed to be
impressed? So blessed!
You're just a helpless geezer who's gotten
too old to help anyone, even himself!
My prosthetic hand!
It was on the verge of breaking
from her attack earlier,
and now I can't get any strength into it!
Just one more push!
Your life as an invalid is about
to come to an end, if you be mean.
There's not a single
way you can defeat me.
You might as well surrender.
What the hell is this?
I might as well what now?
I'm sorry, my hearing isn't
exactly what it once was.
Run that by me one more time, will ya?
It's Kultar!
That was your plan all along!
It wasn't to suffocate me, you
were trying to keep me from moving!
But how?
How did you know there
was Kultar in there?
With my sands power, Hermit
Purple told me everything!
Hey, everyone, look! What is this?
The ashes that foreigners spilled
everywhere when he wrecked the place.
They formed into a
perfect map of the city.
You drew a map with Hermit Purple?
That's how you found the tar?
A map out of incense ashes?
Yeah, now I think even a glorified a
pimple like you should see the difference?
in our fighting experience.
When your opponent starts
boasting, he's already lost.
That shrew is a line from my wilder days.
Like a fine wine, I guess
I just get better with age.
And now, a stand will
defeat another stand.
Next you'll say, please
stop it, I beg you.
Please just stop it, I beg you.
This will hurt me as much as it hurts you.
But children can't depend
on their parents forever.
Once you've grown up, you've got
to learn to live on your own.
Now then, I wonder where that
thing stand user is hiding.
Ah, so, what do you say, Nena, darling?
Shall we seal our new
love with a sweet kiss?
What the hell is this? It's nasty!
What's wrong, Nena?
Ah!
So, she was the empress's
stand user all along.
She was an ugly old troll.
She attached her stand to
me as a tumor with a human
face and camouflaged herself
as a beautiful woman.
You were careless.
She played you like a
damn fiddle, Polnareff.
Oh, oh!
And here I thought we'd finally be
able to sleep in a bed for once.
If the old man hadn't screwed up, he
wouldn't be out here hiding from the cops.
I took care of things.
We can take this car.
Polnareff, you do the driving.
What?
Don't tell me you're still in shock.
I was the one who was
attacked by the stand.
Sure, but I think I'd rather
have gone through that.
All the old paintings on the tomb.
They do the sand dance, don't you know?
If you move too quick, oh well!
They're falling down like a domino.
All the buzzer men by the Nile.
They got their money on
a bed Called crocodiles.
Oh-eh-oh.
They snap their teeth on your cigarette.
Fallen types of the hookah. I say.
Oh-eh-oh.
Walk like an Egyptian.
The blonde waitresses.
Take their trays, spin around
and they cross the floor.
You drop your drink,
then they bring you more.
All the school kids so sick of books.
They're like the punk and the metal band.
When the buzzer rings, they're
walking like an Egyptian.
All the kids in the marketplace say.
Walk
like
an Egyptian?
I guess it's time to say goodbye to India.
I mean, come on, I'm a girl.
So, did you get a look
at the driver's face?
I'm saying we don't need
any more trouble now.
Where'd that come from?
I got a question for you.
You like sumo?